Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXXIV is arranged in 26 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXXV is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXXIV. GROUP INSURANCE
  - Sub-Series 432-0. Group Insurance. General
    - General, 1948-1951 (Box 598b, Folder 1)
      February 1948-51.
    - General, 1934-1948 (Box 598b, Folder 2)
      1934-January 1948.
  - Sub-Series 432-1. Group Insurance. Illinois Central Railroad
    - Case No. L-384, 1932-1937 (Box 598b, Folder 3)
    - General, 1930 (Box 598b, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 432-2. Group Insurance. Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railroad
    - General, 1930-1953 (Box 598b, Folder 5)
    - General, 1932 (Box 598b, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 432-4. Group Insurance. Gulf Coast Lines
    - General, 1932-1943 (Box 598b, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 432-5. Group Insurance. Missouri Pacific Railroad
    - General, 1932-1944 (Box 598b, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 432-6. Group Insurance. Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad
    - General, 1932-1952 (Box 598b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 432-7. Group Insurance. Pere Marquette Railroad
    - General, 1933-1938 (Box 598b, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 432-8. Group Insurance. Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad
    - General, 1939 (Box 598b, Folder 11)
    - General, 1933 (Box 598b, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 432-9. Group Insurance. Atlanta, Birmingham and Coast Railway
    - General, 1933 (Box 598b, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 432-10. Group Insurance. Great Northern Railroad
    - General, 1934-1955 (Box 598b, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 432-11. Group Insurance. New York, Chicago, and St. Louis Railroad
    - General, 1934-1935 (Box 598b, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 432-12. Group Insurance. Southeastern Express Company
    - General, 1934 (Box 598b, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 432-13. Group Insurance. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - General, 1936-1947 (Box 598b, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 432-14. Group Insurance. Northern Pacific Railway
    - General, 1936 (Box 598b, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 432-15. Group Insurance. Texas and Pacific Railway
    - General, 1937 (Box 598b, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 432-16. Group Insurance. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad
    - General, 1939-1955 (Box 598b, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 432-17. Group Insurance. New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad
    - General, 1939 (Box 598b, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 432-18. Group Insurance. Michigan Central Railroad
    - General, 1939 (Box 598b, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 432-19. Group Insurance. Chicago and Northwestern Railway
    - General, 1939 (Box 598b, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 432-20. Group Insurance. Central Railroad of Georgia
    - General, 1942 (Box 598b, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 432-21. Group Insurance. Philadelphia, Bethlehem and New England
    - General, 1950-1954 (Box 598b, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 432-22. Group Insurance. Duluth, Missabe and Iron Range Railroad
    - General, 1950-1954 (Box 598b, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 432-23. Group Insurance. Lake Terminal Railroad
    - General, 1951 (Box 598b, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 432-24. Group Insurance. Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad
    - General, 1953-1955 (Box 598b, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 432-25. Group Insurance. Newburgh and South Shore Railroad
    - General, 1954-1959 (Box 598b, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 432-26. Group Insurance. Piedmont and Northern Railway
    - General, 1953-1955 (Box 598b, Folder 30)
- Series LXXXV. PARCEL POST
  - Sub-Series 434-0. Parcel Post
    - General, 1961-1965 (Box 599a, Folder 1)
      1961-June 1965.
    - General, 1961 (Box 599a, Folder 2)
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 599a, Folder 3)
      August 1959-60.
    - General, 1959 (Box 599a, Folder 4)
      June-July 1959.
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 599a, Folder 5)
      October 1958-May 1959.
    - General, 1958 (Box 599a, Folder 6)
      August-September 1958.
    - General, 1958 (Box 599a, Folder 7)
      June-July 1958.
    - General, 1958 (Box 599a, Folder 8)
      February-May 1958.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 599a, Folder 9)
      April 12, 1957-January 1958.
    - General, 1957 (Box 599a, Folder 10)
      February 19, 1957-April 11, 1957.
    - General, 1956-1957 (Box 599a, Folder 11)
      May 1956-February 18, 1957.
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 599a, Folder 12)
      April 1955-April 1956.
    - General, 1954-1955 (Box 599a, Folder 13)
      July 1954-March 1955.